Thank you.
Oh
This is the main gate with
another urgent report, sir!
What is it this time?
There's a group of heavily armed men
riding giant monsters over the gate!
We need reinforcements!
Please!
Don't waste a second! Let's go!
Hello?
What's wrong?
Answer me!
What's going on here?
Having second thoughts now?
It's too late for that.
All right, guys, you ready to roll?
Aren't you hurt?
Don't worry, these wounds better not.
To Sniper King!
Only four minutes left.
Then the C-Train Rocket
Man is gonna tear through.
Sorry to bother you, but
could you let me pass?
Even if you ask nicely,
you're still an intruder.
And no means no!
Fair enough, but I'll warn you.
Get ready for a fight.
Bring it on, pirate!
Oh!
Ally Robot!
Hey, that's Cheena!
How can we attack him?
It's just a lame, childish trick!
Don't back down!
Ally Robot!
PUN!
Ah, no!
Ally Robot K!
I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
I've had enough of your games.
Your back is wide open.
Bastards!
Bring it down!
There's only one of them!
Damn it!
How does he do that?
I'm in a hurry.
But you'll have more
people to fight later.
See ya!
Hey!
Come back!
He went inside!
After him, quick!
He made it to the main
island! Right! I'm on it!
This is the front gate reporting.
I'm afraid Straw Hat Luffy has
entered the main island, sir.
What?
Why the hell did you let him do that?
What's going on over there?
What about Beam and Cassie?
You can't tell me they got taken out too.
Well, it's actually the middle
of the night right now, sir.
I'm thinking they're probably asleep.
Then stop yapping at me and wake them up.
And if any of the other guards
are sleeping, wake them up too.
Uh, yes, yes, sir.
I don't get why everyone's
pissing their pants over this.
What's one little intruder?
Just let us take care of him.
Nonsense!
This place is the entrance
to the world government.
The judicial island isn't just a
navy base, it's a symbol of justice.
Any idiot should know what it
means to attack Enies Lobby,
and if they don't, we'll
have to teach them.
If we let some dirty band of pirates waltz
in here and take their crew member back,
What does that say about our forces?
We have to beat them.
Our pride is on the line.
Those Straw Hats are going to
learn not to take us lightly.
Hey, gatekeeper, what's
going on at the main gate?
Can you hear me or what?
How many enemies are we looking at here?
Where are they right now?
I need answers, main gate.
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
Hello?
I can't help you if you
don't help me first.
You didn't call me an attacker, can you?
Are you missing?
Go back, son!
Make your way! No!
Mozu, come back! What?
We're just starting!
I can't go wasting my ammo!
Throw in through the doors on the side!
Open that gate!
Push him back before it's too late!
You're in the way!
Mozu, take the left! You've got it!
You're not going anywhere! Huh?
Is that a nose hair?
Actually, it's a cowlick!
Get moving!
Thanks, I owe you one!
I can't my car!
Are you done?
Moses! Kiwi!
We tear ships apart.
You can't expect a little
flock to slow us down.
All right, my side is done! Mine too!
Good!
Let's open those gates!
Herculean destroyers, go!
Don't let them open the gate!
All right, men, let's go!
Whoa!
What is that big hole?
We don't have time for that right now.
Just ignore it!
Everyone make a dash to the next gate!
It's a waterfall!
We did it!
Guys, over here!
I got a plan!
Could you lend me a hand?
Kashi! Oimo!
You have to get up!
We need your help!
The main gate was forced
to open by intruders!
Hey, Oimo, you hear that?
You said the main gate's open.
Oi!
I'm afraid that won't do.
Right, Kashi?
And I was sleeping so well, too.
Work is work. Let's go.
A marinated! No!
These pipsqueeds don't look like much.
Come on, you want to get
back to bed soon, right?
Let's make this quick.
Sounds good.
Whoa, they're, they're giant!
And listen, Twirps,
I don't know what you think you're
doing here, and I don't really care.
Point is, you're getting
crushed if you get in our way.
Right, you tell him, Cassie.
One more step, and we'll
pound your bones into paste.
Dude, this isn't fair.
Nobody told me these guys
had giants for gatekeepers.
They're huge.
They make a Herculean
destroyers look like rugs.
Now, go home.
There's no way I'm letting you through.
Me neither.
Here they come.
The Franky family ain't gonna
back down no matter what.
Ain't that right, you guys?
Do it for Bruce! Yeah!
The Franky family!
Yeah!
All right.
You know what that means. You bet.
Let's do this.
Those giants may be a lot bigger
than us, but we're still pretty big.
We've torn apart ships
ten times their size!
These freaks are nothing!
Go, destroyers!
No!
Our Herculean Destroyers!
They got founded!
Don't you know?
We have the blood of warriors
running through our veins.
An overgrown human is still a human, but
a giant of any size is a fighter at heart.
By the pride of my people,
I won't let you pass!
Boy, me too!
Don't get cold feet, everyone!
We can still do this!
That's right, our big bro is waiting
for us on the other side of that gate!
Yeah!
We'll show those monsters a
fight worthy of bro's name!
Right, Franky family!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy!
How many friends did
you bring with you, huh?
We've got 10,000 soldiers
here at Enies Lobby!
Sorry, but it's just me.
Now get out of my way!
Our bro Franky wouldn't give up at a
time like this and neither will we!
Don't give in!
We gotta clear the way for Rocket Man!
Forget about it.
I won't even let an end through this game.
Oh, the destroyers!
What happened?
You bastards!
Took out our strongest guys
before I even got here!
You'll pass!
Word is dead!
Zambai! Kiwi! Mozu! Galley-La!
Sorry we're late!
Took a little longer than I thought to
get Sodom and Gomorrah ready for land!
Zambai!
They beat the destroyers!
Yeah, I know.
But we don't have time to
patch them up right now.
The only thing that matters
is getting through that gate.
We came here to rescue our big pro,
and that's just what we're gonna do!
Let's rock.
Yeah!
We'll send those big lugs
crashing down. Come on!
You got it, Kiwi!
Here we go!
Hold this mantle and slap!
No action!
Timberheads done!
Cursed noob!
Dial stone!
We nailed luck!
That's a job well done!
Little Runtz, I'll crush you!
Kashi!
All right!
How dare you!
Don't let up, men!
We got one more to go!
What's the current status?
Sir, well,
Kashi and Oimo should be dealing with the
intruders at the main
island gate right now.
I don't suspect they're
having any trouble.
Naturally.
But what about Straw Hat?
Where are we at on that one?
Where are we at?
Uh, this is just an estimate,
but I'd say about 400.
400?
What are you talking about?
Our casualties, sir.
You're not making any sense, man.
You're telling me Straw Hat
has defeated 400 of our guards?
Looks like we lost
about 100 more just now.
No, that number's wrong.
I'll correct it, sir.
You'd better.
Our guards are well-trained.
I'll be damned if one man
could take that many out.
If we have casualties, at
least report them properly.
Right.
Then allow me to report again.
I'd estimate our current
casualties at five...
Five men?
We've only lost five of our guards. Jeez.
How in the world could you
make such an obvious mistake?
Five hundred!
Hmm.
Seems Straw Hat's no threat after all.
He's just running around the
island making a lot of noise.
Well, that's no surprise.
Even he's not stupid enough to take
on that many guards on his own.
Either way, it's only a matter
of time before he's captured.
Good to see you all back!
Chief, Mr.
Lucci's party has arrived! Excellent!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Show them in already!
By the way, Sniper King...
Hey!
That hurt!
You think you could teach me how to
use the cold air feature on this thing?
Sure, it's simple.
I mean, why are you asking me?
You ready, ladies and ships?
The time has finally arrived!
If they don't have those gates
open by now, it ain't gonna happen!
Hurry up and go! Yeah!
I'm gonna need you to
take out that iron fence!
Okay, samurai man?
Just leave it to me.
I'm not sure how to say it.
I'm not even looking at it.
I'm not even looking at it. I'm
looking
at it.
If you want to run away,
the future will run away.
smile and tears?